http://www.sharewarejunction.com/privacy.html

Contact
BusinessCommunicationCursorsEducationGamesInternetMultimedia & Graphic DesignPersonal and HomeProgrammingSecurity & PrivacyUtilitiesWeb AuthoringWeb BrowsersWindows Shell
Privacy Policy
At sharewarejunction.com we strive to protect your privacy and rights. We have set forth this statement to explain the information we collect from you, how we use that information, and your legal rights regarding that information.
Who has access to my information?
The information you provide is controlled by sharewarejunction.com
What information do we collect and how do we use it?
When you choose to contact us through a web form, we need your name, email address, and telephone number. This information is used to contact you if we need to respond to your question.
We use a cookie to store your basket contents during your visit.
We may use your personal information in the prevention and detection of fraud.
We may use your information to administer any prize draws or competitions you may enter.
Do we disclose your information to third parties?
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. If we choose to do so in the future, you will be notified by email of our intentions, and have the right to be removed prior to the disclosure.
Your consent and rights
By using our website you consent to the collection and use of this information by sharewarejunction.com. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted to this page so that you are kept informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Your comments
We welcome comments on our privacy policy. Please email your questions and comments from the contact page.
Most Popular
AttendHRM-HRM-Professional
Bluesoleil cPhoneTool
MacroGamer
All Free PDF Converter
PSpice Student
Easy Grade Pro
TempTale Manager Desktop
Project Timer (Tenda) Nov 28, 2018
Projects required to produce bill so that the employer can see how much time is spent and how...
Magic Uneraser (Monica) Nov 22, 2017
Can recover any files like a magic as it said in its description, works on any file system of...
QILING Disk MasterProfessional (Tejtuniya) Oct
9, 2017
Hard disk is one of the important component in the computer system, it needs to be protected,...
EasyContentTransfer (Udonil) Sep 13, 2017
Camera professionals will have huge advantage from it as all the new photos taken on their...
File Joiner (Jubrain) Aug
5, 2017
For my work I need to carry files of various type in a removable media to give presentation...
Flashnote (Jauhla) Jul 13, 2017
Keep it in your desktop to take quick note on anything like a phone number or email id. Also can...
Slitheris Network Discovery (Webnier) Jun 22, 2017
Scans the whole network for connected devices even the hidden ones and creates a list of them for...
File Commentor (Emily) May
7, 2017
Inserting comments on any files is no more a nightmare, this software makes the task only few...
Canvas Draw for Mac (Rosalin) Apr 16, 2017
Drawing anything for your business or presentation with exciting look is damn easy on you Mac...
iMagic Inventory Software (Emilia) Apr
1, 2017
Maintains the inventory of your business with the products those come in the stock and sold out,...
Top Developers
Lenvica Computer Solutions PvtLtd
IVT Corporation
Devart
MacroGamer
Accessory Software
AllFreeVideoSoft
CoffeeCup Software
Sobolsoft
MagneticOne
Electronics-lab.com
New Developers
HelpSystems LLC.
RealDefense LLC
Koona LLC
Uptrader, Inc.
Spider Financial Corp
VB .NET OCR Team
Christian Findlay and C# ReadExcel Team
.NET Barcode Library Team
SunFirewall
Fornux Inc.
Latest Searches
flat text box
access students data
lecture theatre autocad plans
analog clock wallpaper
background logic pro
imate pocket pc phone
htc hero find drivingdirections
Submit Software
© 1999-2015 Shareware Junction. All rights reserved.
Shareware Junction Network is your source for Shareware, Freeware, Demos, Betas and Pre-Releases. This is the place to come for a first look at the hottest new software. Shareware companies need your support. Beta testing is a unique opportunity to try the latest programs and provide feedback directly to the program developers. The final version of many programs is often determined by suggestions from testers like you. Shareware Junction lets you choose from a variety of these products - all in one convenient location. Use of this site subject to Terms and Privacy Policy
